Dmadd25@gmail.com • Home 716-359-3092

Summary

Customer Service professional with over 5 years' experience in the industry. Ability to build strong rapport with personnel, customers, and associates based on knowledge, professionalism, and integrity. Areas of expertise include preparing sales contracts, processing orders, and maintaining positive customer relations.

Areas of Expertise

- · Proactive customer service, serving as a liaison between technicians and clients.
- · Excellent telephone presence and effective interpersonal skills.
- · Ability to grasp thorough understanding of product features to better serve customers.
- · Computer experience includes MS Word, Excel, Outlook, Access, and Windows.

Experience

Dial America, Amherst, NY

2011 to Present

Customer Service / Sales Representative

Sales representative for a fast-paced company specializing in credit card sales over the telephone. Performed all aspects of customer service and satisfaction, including answering busy multi-line phone system, and providing detailed information for various products.

Heritage Centers, Buffalo, NY

2009 to 2010

Vocational Life Skills Trainer

Taught everyday life skills such as cooking, hygiene and other various tasks so consumers could live on their own

Planned and coordinated various activities and special events for consumers of the day habilitation program

Provide transportation to care programs, and recreational activities; supervise behavior of residents Developed innovative programs and projects for the Developmentally Disabled

Baker Victory Services, Lackawanna, NY

2008 to 2009

One on One Classroom Aide

Provide individualized attention, supervision, and support to students with behavioral and/or emotional problems in order to help them be successful in a classroom setting

Utilize therapeutic crisis intervention to help dissolve and deescalate crisis situations

Support teachers in the classroom setting to sustain a structured, safe environment for learning

Kraft Foods, Batavia, NY

2007 to 2008

Sales/Merchandiser

Demonstrated excellent organizational and time management skills

Exhibited proficiency in managing all aspects of an individual store needs including displays and inventory control

Consistently achieved sales objectives through effective account management and commitment to customer service and satisfaction

ECS Warehouse, Buffalo, NY

2005 to 2007

Sales Manager

Responsible for supervising sales team, maintaining and opening accounts with clients, and ensuring adequate product was available in stores.

Maintained regular contact with regular and prospective customers to solicit orders

Met with customers to demonstrate and explain features of products.

Regarded as a valued contributor in the development, evolution and growth of this company.

Pepsi Bottling Group, Cheektowaga, NY

2003 to 2005

Merchandiser

Responsible for storage room organization and movement of product from storage to the sales floor Responsible for product merchandising within large volume stores including freshness rotation, display set up and maintenance, cooler stocking/rotation

Provided recommendations and answered questions for customers based on their specific needs and interests

Education

Hilbert College, Hamburg, NY Associate, Criminal Justice

2003

Erie Community College, Orchard Park, NY [Degree], Information Technology Currently taking classes to get CISCO certification. (CCNA) Cisco certification will be completed in summer of 2011.

2012

Additional Skills

- Internet Technology
- Internet Explorer
- MS DOS